PEQuestions = [
    {
        "question": "What does SOAP stand for s____, o____, a____, p____",
        "answer": "subjective, objective, assessment, plan",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Normal temperature ranges from ____-____F",
        "answer": "98.6-100.3",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Normal blood pressure is <____ and <____",
        "answer": "120, 80",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Elevated blood pressure is ____-____ and <",
        "answer": "120-129, 80",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stage 1 hypertension is ____-____ OR ",
        "answer": "130-139, 80-89",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stage 2 hypertension is >= ____ OR >= ",
        "answer": "140, 90",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hypertensive crisis is >= ____ AND/OR > ____",
        "answer": "180, 120",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal range for heart rate or pulse is ____-____ beats/min",
        "answer": "60-90",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal respiratory rate is ____-____ breaths/min ",
        "answer": "12-20",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pain is considered the ____th vital sign",
        "answer": "5th",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The skin is examined for l____, s____, b____, r____, m____, s____ t____ and e____",
        "answer": "lesions, scars, bruises, rash, moles, skin turgor, elasticity",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one is not a part of a head inspection",
		"choices": "inspection of hair and scalp, palpation of the skull for any normalities, inspection of face for symmetry or trauma",
		"answer": "palpation of the skull for any normalities",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one is not a part of an eye inspection",
		"choices": "inspection of sclera and conjunctiva, size/shape/symmetry of pupils, dark reaction, accomodation",
        "answer": "dark reaction",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "P____, E____, R____, R____, L____, A____",
        "answer": "pupils, equal, round, reactive, light, accomodation",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "E____, O____, M____, I____",
        "answer": "extra, ocular, movements, intact",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one is not a part of ear inspection",
		"choices": "check for auditory acuity, inspect inner ear, inspect ear canal and tymphanic membranes",
        "answer": "inspect inner ear",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one is not a part of nose inspection",
		"choices": "inspect anterior and inferior surfaces, note symmetry or deformity, test for nasal obstruction, inspect nasal mucosa and septum, palpitate frontal and maxillary septum",
        "answer": "palpitate frontal and maxillary septum",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one is not a part of the mouth and throat structure",
		"choices": "lips, oral mucus, tongue, gums and teeth, palate, tonsils, pharynx, trachea",
        "answer": "trachea",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one is not a neck inspection",
		"choices": "palpate the lymph nodes bilaterally using a linear motion, inspect thyroid gland, inspect jugular vein to detect jugular venous distension",
        "answer": "palpate the lymph nodes bilaterally using a linear motion",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "The first heart sound lub is heard at the ____, and the ____ and ____ valve close",
        "answer": "apex, mitral, tricuspid",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The second heart sound dub is heard at the ____, and the ____ and ____ valve close",
        "answer": "base, pulmonic, aortic",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The S3/4 gallop is abnormal becuase it may be a sign of ____ failure, ____ regurgitation ",
        "answer": "heart, mitral",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "A murmur is benign or pathological ____ blood flow",
        "answer": "turbulent",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "A rub is ____ friction",
        "answer": "myocardial",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 areas for listening to the heart is A (right 2nd intercostal space)____, P(left 2nd intercostal space) ____, E (left 3rd intercostal space)____, T(left 4th intercostal)____, M(left 5th intercostal)____",
        "answer": "aortic, pulmonic, ERB, tricuspid, mitral",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which physical examination does not overlap with the CV exam",
		"choices": "JVD, clubbing, cyanosis, peripheral edema, palpitation",
		"answer": "palpitation",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the four steps for a respiratory exam I____, P____, P____, A____",
        "answer": "inspection, palpitation, percussion, auscultation",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Inspection involves noting the skin for any m____, s____, r____, h____",
        "answer": "marks, scars, rashes, hernia",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The contour of the abdomen is observed to see if it is f____, r____, b____",
        "answer": "flat, round, bloated",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Auscultation is used to check for b____ motility, and to listen for b____ on a____ and e____ area",
        "answer": "bowel, bruits, aorta, epigastric",
        "type": "fill"
	},
    {
        "question": "Bruits is a murmur like sound that is caused by t____ blood flow indicating an o____",
        "answer": "turbulent, obstruction",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Percussion is used to check the amount and distribution of g____ in the abdomen, and helps to identify masses that are s____ or f____ filled, estimate the size of the l____ and s____",
        "answer": "gas, solid, fluid, liver, spleen",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "All four quadrants need to be percussed to assess d____ and r____",
        "answer": "dullness, resonance",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Light/deep palpation helps to identify m____, t____, ",
        "answer": "masses, tenderness",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Musculoskeletal inspection is used to check for d____, s____, r____ of motion",
        "answer": "deformities, symmetry, range",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Neurological exam is used to determine level of consciousness: a____, l____, s____, c____",
        "answer": "alert, lethargic, stuporous, comatose",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 orientation questions asked are p____, p____, t____, s____",
        "answer": "person, place, time, situation",
        "type": "fill"
    }
]